♪ Ending ♪
What can I do now?
I can't be anything or nothing
I'm back.
Love! The recap of our supremely disorganized day is over!
Crackle, crackle, crackle!
Hugh, hugh, hugh, hugh, hugh, hugh, hugh, hugh, hugh, hugh.
The chorus is in an incredibly high key
I struggled a little bit, but the lyrics were really good.
but the lyrics are really good and the song really sticks with you.
It's a song that really sticks with you.
I would like to recommend this song to everyone.
I hope this song will be a colorful part of your daily life.
It's ridiculous
You're just you
Because you made me laugh
That's right
Then love me! We're having a very bad day...
What kind of music is it?
Yes, it is.
This one is...
It's like, "Love me already!
But the lyrics are really good.
I was really surprised.
I love the second chorus.
"What does it mean to have no one to turn to?
That's great!
It's really good.
I love it!
The lyrics are so good!
I really...
We're really not ourselves.
Within ourselves.
It really is.
You know...
What can I do now?
I don't know if I can.
I'll never be anything.
That's ridiculous.
You laughed at me and told me that you're just you.
Ha!
Huh.
This one laughed at me.
That's nice.
We have a good relationship.
I was trying to be accepted by someone.
If you can get in without losing sight of who you really are...
Cool.
I really like the lyrics.
They're really good.
It's a little bit more like "Glory" or something.
Yes, it's the lead song.
But this time it's a little different from Glory.
It's a bit different from Glory this time, because it's really about our youth, or our current state of mind.
I think that if we show ourselves as we are now
I think this song will really resonate with everyone.
I really think so!
Please look forward to the day when we'll be extremely scattered!
By the time this goes up...
I wonder if I'll have a boyfriend by the time this goes up.
Please listen to it a lot, a lot, a lot!
Please love us
Yes, I do.
Okay, bye-bye.
Bye-bye
If love, hate, or anything else is a cry
Even in our absurd world
We can go beyond
We can love
High
We just finished recording the lead song.
This song is probably the hardest song we've ever recorded.
The level of love band music is getting higher and higher
We are really trying our best to keep up with it!
The chorus is very high!
It's so high that even when I sing it
I was really anxious about whether people would listen to it or not.
But I tried my best to make it good.
Please listen to it as much as you can!
Even if the end will come someday
If it's a cry of love, hate, or whatever
Even in our absurd world
We can go beyond
I can love you
Yes, I've just finished recording
I've just finished recording
It was really high and very, very difficult, and the hammoly was also very, very high and very, very difficult.
It was very difficult to switch between back voice and my own voice, so it was a very difficult song.
But I did my best to make it resonate with everyone, so please listen to it!
But maybe it's me who lives in your heart.
I'm singing so high, my throat is in a high position, my voice is so high right now.
Yeah, well, keep it high and keep talking.
Oh, no!
Come on, come on.
Thanks!
We're a mess.
I guess we'll always live next door
If our talent value is anything to go by.
Uh, too expensive.
I'll be back in a little bit.
I'm trying to sing better.
So that I can sing high notes with ease
I'm going to do my best.
So please support me.
So long.
Bye bye.
Whatever the value of our talents
We can change the future no matter what clouds rise
We're done.
Thank you for your hard work.
That was the hardest thing I've ever done.
It took me so long.
This is the hardest one yet.
This is the hardest part.
It's so hard!
By far, the hardest one so far!
It's like...
Oh, my God!
What kind of clouds can change even the bright future
So we finished recording!
It's the lead song, right?
Well, I thought it was a difficult song in the rubber this time.
I thought it was a difficult song to record.
I was a little anxious about it, but
I think it turned out to be a good piece of work.
I see.
Well, we've finally started working on our second album.
We'll be working on it more and more, recoding, choreographing, etc.
We are very excited to see what kind of wonderful work we will end up with.
Well, that's all for now, let's wrap things up.
Haruma-san, please end on a cool note.
Please look forward to the album!
I'm sure you'll get a great one!
I don't have the vocabulary... if I didn't finish...
I'll look at the camera one last time.
I'll be watching the camera one last time, so look forward to it!
Thank you for watching.
I don't care if I'm a little off, I'll sing for the rest of my life.
We're here for sure now
Love us, our extremely messed up selves
I think we'll always live next to each other
If our talents are worth anything
What clouds can change even the bright future
Love our extremely scattered days
Even if one day the end will come
If love, hate, or a mouth is anything but a cry
Even in our absurd world
I can love you, I can love you
Love you, for our days are extremely scattered
Thank you for watching!